<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 10/4/2014 4:10:59 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_AMERICA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your blue jeans and listening to your Rock and Roll. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ARABIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your keffiyeh and painting arabesques. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_AZTEC_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now drinking your xocolatl and eating your tacos. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_CHINA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your porcelain and watching your wuxia movies. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_EGYPT_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your papyri and wearing your makeup. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ENGLAND_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now drinking your tea and listening to your Britpop. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_FRANCE_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now eating your cheese and wearing your perfumes. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_GERMANY_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your cars and drinking your beer. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_GREECE_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now dancing the Sirtaki and watching your tragedies. The real tragedy is that the rest of the world will soon succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_INDIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now practicing Yoga and watching your Bollywood movies. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_IROQUOIS_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now playing Lacrosse and smoking your tobacco. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_JAPAN_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your kimono and watching your anime. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_OTTOMAN_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your fezzes and eating your doner kebab. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_PERSIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now eating your pilaf and buying your rugs. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ROME_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your togas and watching your gladiatorial games. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_RUSSIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your matryoshka dolls and drinking your vodka. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_SIAM_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your pha nung and practicing Muay Thai. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_SONGHAI_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your bogolan shirts and playing the Kora. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_BABYLON_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now obsessed with your astrology and believe their fates are written in the stars. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_MONGOL_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now playing the Morin Khuur while singing with their throats. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_INCA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your alpaca clothing and chewing your coca leaves. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_SPAIN_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now dancing the flamenco and watching your bull fights. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_POLYNESIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your shirts and doing the hula dance. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_DENMARK_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our children are now growing up with your fairy tales and playing with your plastic bricks. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_KOREA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your electronics and playing your MMORPGs. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_AUSTRIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your Wiener schnitzels and drinking your energy drinks. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_BYZANTIUM_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now spending their days playing backgammon and making mosaics. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_CARTHAGE_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>"Your Tyrian purple is now the new black among my people. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_CELTS_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your kilts and drinking your stout. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ETHIOPIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now drinking your coffee and wearing dreadlocks. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_HUNS_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now regressing toward your barbaric, nomadic way of life. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_MAYA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people have now adopted your calendar and predict catastrophes for the near future. I predict that the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_NETHERLANDS_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your tulips and your clogs. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_SWEDEN_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your furniture and listening to your Death Metal. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ASSYRIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now drinking your Arak and dancing the Khigga. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_BRAZIL_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now drinking your Caipirinha and listening to your Bossa Nova. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_INDONESIA_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your batik clothes and listening to your Gamelan music. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_MOROCCO_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now eating your couscous and watching your belly dancers. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_POLAND_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now eating your pierogi and dancing the Mazurka. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_PORTUGAL_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your azulejos and listening to your Fado. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_SHOSHONE_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your feathered war bonnets and consuming peyote. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_VENICE_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your glass trinkets and your masks. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_GENERIC_ZULU_INFLUENTIAL_ON_AI_1">
			<Text>Our people are now buying your vuvuzelas and your ceremonial shields. I worry the rest of the world will also succumb to the influence of your culture.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>