<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<!--As of Version 2, this mod supports both English and German text.-->
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Add names for each new religion. -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_AMADHLOZI">
			<Text>Amadhlozi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NEMESUMAGU">
			<Text>Nemesumagu</Text>
		<!--Add adjective forms for each new religion. Allows compatibility with Lex's "Civ Names by Policy" (which I use).-->
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_AMADHLOZI_ADJ">
			<Text>Amadhlozinic</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NEMESUMAGU_ADJ">
			<Text>Nemesumaguan</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Add civolopedia pages for each new religion. -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_AMADHLOZI_PEDIA">
			<Text>While traditional Zulu animism lacks a defined term, "Amadhlozi" is one name for this old faith, the word itself meaning "the ancestral spirits" in IsiZulu. Never truly beyond the world of mortals, these ancestral spirits lie at the core of traditional Zulu society, ghostly beings who may return to their decedents at any time to bring dreams, good fortune, illness, or punishment. The living mediate themselves with the dead through traditional healers called "sangomas", who use divination and magic to restore health to the sick, place protections upon warriors, guide group rituals, and undo the misdeeds of witches: those who use magic maliciously. While animistic, Zulu religion is also polytheistic. The god Nkulunkulu is the creator and head of the Zulu pantheon, though he does not deal in the everyday lives of mortals; only one's ancestors do that.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Upon arriving in Zululand, European colonizers sought to covert the Zulu and other local peoples to Christianity. Although over time many Zulu came to embrace the Christian faith, most refused to abandon their traditional ways and only accepted Christianity by blending it syncretically. Of the 10 million Zulu living in South Africa today, the majority practice Christianity alongside some aspect of traditional Zulu religion, and 60% still habitually seek the help of sangomas to heal illnesses.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NEMESUMAGU_PEDIA">
			<Text>As diverse as it is ancient, Nemesumagu is the traditional way of the Shoshoni peoples. Like many Native American faiths, Nemesumagu includes a wide array of different beliefs that are typically mutable over time. There are many versions of the Shoshoni creation myth. Some believe that the Sun created both Heaven and Earth, others believe that the trickster Coyote or his noble brother Wolf was the ultimate creator, while still others perceive the world's creation by the kindly spirit "Our Father". Whoever the creator, the Shoshone traditionally seek aid and guidance from these and other benevolent spirits. Before one is able to receive aid, they must purify themselves by sitting in a sweat lodge. Generally, tribes don't have designated priests, so individuals seek the divine on their own terms, particularly through vision quests and reading dreams. Tribes do however have shamans who treat illnesses with chants and herbalism, and in grave cases seek out spiritual assistance by fasting in the wilderness until receiving guiding visions. In some tribal bands, women may serve in the role of shaman.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Dances are indispensable to the practice of Nemesumagu and are key to its gradual development. The Shoshone recognize many dances, each performing a particular function. The Round Dance marks when food is abundant. The Father Dance thanks the Creator for his good works. The Shoshone historically redefined their beliefs by incorporating dances learned from the Plains Nations to the east. In the early 19th century the Shoshone absorbed the Sun Dance, and dance about sacrifice and renewal performed annually before each summer hunt. Participants in the Sun Dance typically pray and fast, while dancers do nothing but dance for four days. In some tribes, participant warriors suspend themselves from metal skewers to prove their worth to the spirits. Toward the late 19th century the Shoshone adopted the Ghost Dance, a movement that swept across the United States among tribes weary of American dominance. Participants danced and prayed to reconnect with their ancestors and to prepare for the day when an apocalypse would wipe the white men from the earth, when all the dead ancestors would return, and when native traditions would finally be restored. While wildly popular, the dance dwindled in the aftermath of the Wounded Knee Massacre.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]As American settlers, miners, and soldiers eventually overtook the Shoshone, many aspects of Nemesumagu crumbled. The Shoshone tentatively took up Christianity and Mormonism, while little by little the dances and shamanic customs languished on reservations. Enough has survived however that the remaining 10,000 or so Shoshone today have been able to make great steps towards revitalizing old beliefs and preserving their heritage for future generations.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<!--Add text for German, Thanks to Lukas.-->
	<Language_DE_DE>
		<!-- Add names for each new religion. -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_AMADHLOZI">
			<Text>Amadhlozi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NEMESUMAGU">
			<Text>Nemesumagu</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Add civolopedia pages for each new religion. -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_AMADHLOZI_PEDIA">
			<Text>Wärend der traditionelle Zulu Animismus keinen definirten Terminus besitzt, ist "Amadhlozi" ein Ausdruck für diesen alten Glauben. Das Wort selbst bedeutet "Die Geister der Vorfahren" in ihrer Sprache IsiZulu. Die Welt der Sterblichen niemals wirklich verlassend, stehen diese Geister im Zentrum der traditionellen Zulu Gesellschaft. Diese geisterhaften Wesen können jederzeit zurück kommen zu ihren Nachfahren, ihnen Träume bringen, Glück aber auch Krankheiten oder Strafen. Die Lebenden sprechen mit den Toten durch Vermittler, welche "Sangomas" genannt werden. Diese Heiler verwenden Beschwörungen und Magie um Gesundheit wieder her zu stellen, Krieger zu beschützen, Gruppenrituale durch zu führen und Flüche von Hexen auf zu heben, welche diese Magie zum Schaden verwenden. Die Zulu Religion ist animistisch, aber auch polytheistisch. Die Gottheit Nkulunkulu ist der Schöpfer und der Kopf des Zulu Pantheons, mischt sich jedoch nicht in das Alltagsleben der Sterblichen ein, nur die Geister der Vorfahren tun das.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bei eintreffen der Europäer im Land der Zulu, versuchten die Kolonialmächte sofort das Christentum zu etablieren. Obwohl nach und nach viele Zulu sich zu der neuen Religion bekannten, lehnten die meisten es ab ihre althergebrachten Traditionen auf zu geben. Von den 10 Milionen Zulu die heute in Südafrika leben praktizieren die Mehrheit das Christentum Seite an Seite mit vielen Aspekten der alten Traditionen, 60 % suchen z.B. die Hilfe von Sangomas auf, um Krankheiten zu heilen.</Text>		
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGION_NEMESUMAGU_PEDIA">
			<Text>Ebenso vielfältig wie alt, ist Nemesumagu, der traditionelle Weg des Volkes der Schoschonen. Wie viele Glaubensrichtungen der ureingeborenen Amerikaner schließt Nemesumagu ein weites Spektrum verschiedener Vorstellungen ein, die sich im Lauf der Zeit auch veränderten. Es gibt verschiedene Schöpfungs-mythen, z.B. glauben einige das die Sonne, Erde und Himmel erschaffen hat, andere glauben das der betrügerische Koyote oder sein edler Bruder, der Wolf die Schöpfer waren, während andere wieder den Großen Geist "Unser Vater" als Ursprung sehen.Wer auch immer der Schöpfer ist, die Schoschonen suchen Anleitung und Führung bei diesen und anderen verehrten Geistern. Bevor man Führung von diesen Geistern erhalten kann, muß man sich reinigen, was die Schoschonen durch schwitzen in einer Saunahütte taten. Im Allgemeinen hatten die Stämme keine designierten Priester, jedes Individuum suchte selbst nach Leitung in Visionen und Träumen. Die Stämme hatten jedoch Schamanen, die durch Fasten in der Wildniss nach Visionen suchten, und mit Kräutermedizin und Gesängen Krankheiten zu heilen suchten. In einigen Stämmen waren auch Frauen in der Rolle eines Schamanen.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Tänze sind unverzichtbar in den Praktiken des Nemesumagu und das Schlüsselelement ihrer Entwicklung. Der Kreistanz markiert die Abwesenheit von Nahrung, der Tanz des Vaters ist eine Danksagung an den Schöpfer für seine gute Arbeit. Die Schoschonen haben in ihrer Geschichte die Tänze der Präriestämme aus dem Osten übernommen, so z.B. den Sonnentanz, den sie im frühen 19. Jahrhundert übernahmen, als Erneuerungs- und Opferritual um Erfolg vor jeder Jagd im Sommer zu Beschwören.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Teilnehmer dieses Rituals beten und fasten, wärend die Tänzer nichts tun als vier tage lang zu tanzen. In einigen Stämmen durchbohrten sich einige Teilnehmer mit Metalspießen, um ihren Wert vor den Geistern zu beweisen. Im späteren 19. Jahrundert übernahmen die Schoschonen den Geistertanz, eine Bewegung die sich im Angesicht der US-Dominanz über alle Stämme Amerikas ausbreitete. Die Teilnehmer beteten und tanzten, um sich mit ihren Vorfahren zu vereinen, und um sich vor zu bereiten für den Tag, an dem eine Apokalypse den Weißen Mann von der Erde tilgen sollte, wenn alle Geister der Vohrfahren zurückkehren und die alten Bräuche wieder her gestellt sein sollten. Obwohl er extrem populär war, verschwand der Geistertanz nach dem Wounded Knee Massaker wieder. Nachdem immer mehr Siedler, Minenarbeiter und Soldaten im Schoschonenland auftauchten sind viele Aspekte des Nemesumagu verschwunden. Die Schoschonen begangen langsam das Christentum und das Mormonentum zu übernehmen, die Tänze und Rituale beschränkten sich nur noch auf die Reservate. Dennoch hat genug davon überlebt, daß die ca 10,000 übrigen Schoschonen von heute ein Wiederaufleben ihrer alten Kultur, ihres Erbes und ihres Glaubens erleben und für kommende Generationen erhalten.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_DE_DE>
</GameData>