<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/16/2014 8:12:23 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Technologies>
		<Row>
			<Type>TECH_SPACE_MINING</Type>
			<Cost>18000</Cost>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_TECH_SPACE_MINING_TITLE</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_TECH_SPACE_MINING_DESC</Civilopedia>
			<Help>A Future Technology</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>23</GridX>
			<GridY>3</GridY>
			<Quote>TXT_KEY_TECH_SPACE_MINING_QUOTE</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>2</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
		</Row>
	<Row>
		<Type>TECH_NEUROTECHNOLOGY</Type>
		<Cost>18000</Cost>
		<Description>Neurotechnology</Description>
		<Civilopedia>Augmented cognition (AugCog) is a research field at the frontier between human-computer interaction, psychology, ergonomics and neuroscience, that aims at creating revolutionary human-computer interactions. The creation of such interactions stems from the ability of technology to measure human information processing and a user’s cognitive state. Various research projects aim at evaluating in real-time the cognitive state of a user, and this is most commonly evaluated by using either EEG or fNIR systems. Another main concept of AugCog is to design closed-loop systems to modulate information flow with respect to the user's cognitive capacity.</Civilopedia>
		<Help>A Future Technology</Help>
		<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
		<Trade>true</Trade>
		<GridX>24</GridX>
		<GridY>5</GridY>
		<Quote>
			The human brain has 100 billion neurons, each neuron connected to 10 thousand other neurons. Sitting on your shoulders is the most complicated object in the known universe.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Michio Kaku
		</Quote>
		<PortraitIndex>5</PortraitIndex>
		<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Type>TECH_OCEAN_MINING</Type>
		<Cost>18000</Cost>
		<Description>Deep Sea Mining</Description>
		<Civilopedia>Deep sea mining is a relatively new mineral retrieval process that takes place on the ocean floor. Ocean mining sites are usually around large areas of polymetallic nodules or active and extinct hydrothermal vents at about 1,400 - 3,700 m below the ocean’s surface. The vents create sulfide deposits, which contain valuable metals such as silver, gold, copper, manganese, cobalt, and zinc. The deposits are mined using either hydraulic pumps or bucket systems that take ore to the surface to be processed. As with all mining operations, deep sea mining raises questions about potential environmental impact on surrounding areas. Environmental advocacy groups such as Greenpeace have argued that seabed mining should not be permitted in most of the world's oceans because of the potential for damage to deepsea ecosystems.</Civilopedia>
		<Help>A Future Technology</Help>
		<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
		<Trade>true</Trade>
		<GridX>23</GridX>
		<GridY>0</GridY>
		<Quote>
			The offshore ocean area under U.S. jurisdiction is larger than our land mass, and teems with plant and animal life, mineral resources, commerce, trade, and energy sources.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Tom Allen
		</Quote>
		<PortraitIndex>1</PortraitIndex>
		<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
	</Row>
		<Row>
			<Type>TECH_HYPERSONIC_TRAVEL</Type>
			<Cost>18000</Cost>
			<Description>Hypersonic Speed</Description>
			<Civilopedia>
				While conventional turbo and ramjet engines are able to remain reasonably efficient up to Mach 5.5, some ideas for very high-speed flight above Mach 6 are also sometimes discussed, with the aim of reducing travel times down to one or two hours anywhere in the world. These vehicle proposals very typically either use rocket or scramjet engines; pulse detonation engines have also been proposed.
			</Civilopedia>
			<Help>Unlocks the Hypersonic promotion for aircraft.</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>23</GridX>
			<GridY>7</GridY>
			<Quote>
				If everything seems under control, you're just not going fast enough.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Mario Andretti
			</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>3</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
		</Row>
		
		<!--<Row>
			<Type>TECH_RENEWABLE_ENERGY</Type>
			<Cost>11500</Cost>
			<Description>Renewable Energy</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_DESC</Civilopedia>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_HELP</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>16</GridX>
			<GridY>0</GridY>
			<Quote>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_QUOTE</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>4</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>CIV_COLOR_ATLAS_BTF</IconAtlas>
		</Row>-->
		<Row>
			<Type>TECH_RAILGUN</Type>
			<Cost>18000</Cost>
			<Description>Railgun</Description>
			<Civilopedia>
				In 1918, French inventor Louis Octave Fauchon-Villeplee invented an electric cannon which is an early form of railgun. He filed for a US patent on 1 April 1919, which was issued in July 1922 as patent no. 1,421,435 Electric Apparatus for Propelling Projectiles. In his device, two parallel busbars are connected by the wings of a projectile, and the whole apparatus surrounded by a magnetic field. By passing current through busbars and projectile, a force is induced which propels the projectile along the bus-bars and into flight. In 1944, during World War II, Joachim Hänsler of Germany's Ordnance Office built the first working railgun, and an electric anti-aircraft gun was proposed. By late 1944 enough theory had been worked out to allow the Luftwaffe's Flak Command to issue a specification, which demanded a muzzle velocity of 2,000 m/s (6,600 ft/s) and a projectile containing 0.5 kg (1.1 lb) of explosive. The guns were to be mounted in batteries of six firing twelve rounds per minute, and it was to fit existing 12.8 cm FlaK 40 mounts. It was never built. When details were discovered after the war it aroused much interest and a more detailed study was done, culminating with a 1947 report which concluded that it was theoretically feasible, but that each gun would need enough power to illuminate half of Chicago. During 1950, Sir Mark Oliphant, an Australian physicist and first director of the Research School of Physical Sciences at the new Australian National University, initiated the design and construction of the world's largest (500 megajoule) homopolar generator. This machine was operational from 1962 and was later used to power a large-scale railgun that was used as a scientific experiment.
			</Civilopedia>
			<Help>Unlocks 3 powerful naval railgun promotions.</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>23</GridX>
			<GridY>8</GridY>
			<Quote>
				I am proud of the fact that I never invented weapons to kill.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Thomas A. Edison
			</Quote>
			<IconAtlas>RAILGUN_DESTROYER_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>0</PortraitIndex>
			<!--<PortraitIndex>4</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>-->
		</Row>
		<!--<Row>
			<Type>TECH_ARCOLOGY</Type>
			<Cost>11500</Cost>
			<Description>Arcology</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_DESC</Civilopedia>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_HELP</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>17</GridX>
			<GridY>1</GridY>
			<Quote>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_QUOTE</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>4</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>CIV_COLOR_ATLAS_BTF</IconAtlas>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Type>TECH_SYNTHETIC_LIFE</Type>
			<Cost>11500</Cost>
			<Description>Synthetic Life</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_DESC</Civilopedia>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_HELP</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>16</GridX>
			<GridY>1</GridY>
			<Quote>TXT_KEY_TECH_AI_QUOTE</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>4</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>CIV_COLOR_ATLAS_BTF</IconAtlas>
		</Row>-->
		<Row>
			<Type>TECH_HYDROPONICS</Type>
			<Cost>18000</Cost>
			<Description>Hydroponics</Description>
			<Civilopedia>It is estimated that by the year 2050, close to 80% of the world’s population will live in urban areas and the total population of the world will increase by 3 billion people. A very large amount of land may be required depending on the change in yield per hectare. Scientists are concerned that this large amount of required farmland will not be available and that severe damage to the earth will be caused by the added farmland. Vertical farms, if designed properly, may eliminate the need to create additional farmland and help create a cleaner environment.</Civilopedia>
			<Help>A Future Technology</Help>
			<Era>ERA_FUTURE</Era>
			<Trade>true</Trade>
			<GridX>23</GridX>
			<GridY>2</GridY>
			<Quote>Urban farming is not only possible, it is crucial. But it can't be like the farming techniques of yore.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]- Homaro Cantu
			</Quote>
			<PortraitIndex>0</PortraitIndex>
			<IconAtlas>FUTURE_AGE_TECH_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
		</Row>
	</Technologies>
	<Technology_PrereqTechs>
	<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_NEUROTECHNOLOGY</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_NANOTECHNOLOGY</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_OCEAN_MINING</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_NAVIGATION</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_FUTURE_TECH</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_SPACE_MINING</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_FUTURE_TECH</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_NANOTECHNOLOGY</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
	</Technology_PrereqTechs>
	<Technology_ORPrereqTechs>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_SPACE_MINING</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_OCEAN_MINING</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYPERSONIC_TRAVEL</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_RAILGUN</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYDROPONICS</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_NANOTECHNOLOGY</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_INTERNET</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_GLOBALIZATION</TechType>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_OCEAN_MINING</PrereqTech>
		</Row>
		</Technology_ORPrereqTechs>
	<Technology_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_OCEAN_MINING</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_PRODUCTION</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYDROPONICS</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_GROWTH</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYDROPONICS</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_EXPANSION</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>20</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYPERSONIC_TRAVEL</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_WONDER</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>2</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_SPACE_MINING</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_NUKE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_SPACE_MINING</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_SPACESHIP</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYPERSONIC_TRAVEL</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>20</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_HYPERSONIC_TRAVEL</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_SPACESHIP</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_RAILGUN</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_RAILGUN</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_NUCLEAR_FUSION</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_NEUROTECHNOLOGY</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_SPACESHIP</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_NEUROTECHNOLOGY</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>30</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<TechType>TECH_FUTURE_TECH</TechType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_SPACESHIP</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>10</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Technology_Flavors>
</GameData>